So now that we have seen how to program Mifare classic cards and we have also seen how to secure these
cards and how to find vulnerabilities using prox.
Mark three Now we are going to see a practical demonstration using Mifare classic card, and we are
using the same sketch as before in our earlier videos.
But we have changed the code.
So let's just go through the example first and then we will go through the code as well.
So over here you can see the practical example of the sketch.
And let's just place Mifare classic card over here.
And as you can see, it's reading the Uuid as well as name and the position, right?
So let's just try another card.
Right.
So this is the practical example of Mifare classic card.
And we are using block to store the data, the position data and the name data.
And we will go through the code once after after this example.
So.
Over here.
You can notice the Uuid of this card.
And I have a magic card as well.
And I have also cloned the ID of this card.
And I'm going to place this card on the module.
So as you can see, the Uuid is same.
So as you can see, the same.
But still we are not able to login or validate this card.
Have a look at the valid card one more time.
So the Uid is same, but still this card is invalid.
Have a look at one more time.
And this is the valid card.
And we are getting the name and position using this card.
So now we will go through the code of this example in our next video.